Michael Delu

Los Angeles, CA michaeldelu7_pnn@indeedemail.com 13238101316

Dependable manager with experience in warehouse management and employee supervision. Skilled at managing inventory control, shipping & receiving, customer relations and safety & compliance. Skills include computer networking, analytical thinking and creative problem solving. Able to apply customer service concepts to improve user experience for clients, employees and administration.

#readytowork

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Preload Supervisor

UPS - Los Angeles, CA September 2018 to Present

- Manage, plan, organize, and direct all employees during pre-load operation
- Organize workflow and ensure that employees understand their duties or delegated tasks
- Monitor employee productivity and provide constructive feedback and coaching
- Ensure employees follow company policies and procedures
- Motivate team members and create strategies to boost productivity
- · Prepare and submit daily reports

Debt Collection Specialist

Virtuoso Sourcing Group - Tempe, AZ January 2018 to August 2018

- Answer borrower questions regarding problems with their account.
- Use computers, automated systems and a variety of software.
- Maintain confidentiality with a high level of trustworthiness.
- Successfully complete training and retain information that is taught.
- Maintain call quality and compliance.

SDA Media Relations Intern

Arizona State Athletic Department - Tempe, AZ January 2016 to June 2018

- Maintain sport and athlete files for archival purposes
- Write press releases for media outlets and help maintain TheSunDevils.com
- Work sporting events as assigned, and assist sport-specific SID with duties
- Distribute to media reps statistical information at sporting events
- · Assist with photo and video shoots by coordinating student athletes for assigned photo shoots
- Transcribe press conferences for media outlets
- Adhere to NCAA and Pac-12 rules and regulations, as well as the policies and procedures of the department, the University, and the Arizona Board of Regents.

• Will perform other duties as assigned.

Education

Bachelor's in Communications

Arizona State University-Tempe - Tempe, AZ January 2016 to June 2018

Associate in Communications

El Camino Community College - Torrance, CA August 2013 to May 2015

Skills

- Media Relations
- Microsoft Word
- Computer Skills
- Customer Service
- Excel
- Organizational Skills
- Time Management
- Oral Communication